本字幕OCR于网络上的RMVB版本，版权归原字幕组所有
谢绝转载字幕至射手网等其他网站或者论坛
字幕可能有漏抓几句，翻译凑合看
我一会跟parker说说今天我升职的事
I'm going to talk to
Parker about my promotion today.
你比我提前两周工作
In the worst-case scenario
you're two weeks ahead of me,
你在Mraisr搞到相当拉风的小房子
you get a gorgeous little
apartment in the Marais.
如果我不想在Marasi住呢
What if I don't want
to live in the Marais?
Weston：那我们就去别的地方住吧
We could live
somewhere else, then.
是吗？是啊
Yeah?
Yeah.
我们可能去底特律
We could go to Detroit.
底特律？
Detroit?
是啊，可以见见我爸妈
Yeah, you could
meet my mom and dad.
可以见见我妹妹，她开了个面包房哦
You can meet my sister.
She owns a bakery,
会让你越吃越胖的
and she will
make you fat.
在我不得不回医院之前我只有六个小时了
I have six hours before I have
to go back to the hospital.
想跟我再回去补一觉吗
You want to go
back into bed with me?
Weston：当然
I do.
但是紧接着要开一早上的会啊
But I got back-to-back
meetings all morning.
太逊了
Too bad for you.
Weston：嗯，我知道
Yeah, I know.
但是我得进去了
But I got to get in.
可能里面已经有25个人了
There's probably
already 25 people
在门外排队等候
lined up outside
the door, waiting.
你说法语的时候真是帅呆了
I love when
you speak French.
操作员：卫星通信检查
Satcom check.
93回话，Victor号接2线
Echo Nine Three
Victor Echo Two.
房东：基地 中心
Ops Center.
Weston：这里是7-R号"藏匿之所",我们要开始工作了
This is safe house 7-R.
We're open for business.
确认
Confirmed.
有预订吗？
Any reservations?
无申请注册
Nothing in
the registry.
进入者呢
Walk-ins?
预测不会 三小时重新确认
Not expected.
Reconfirm in three hours.
收到
Understood.
Barlow：Matt?竟然是你,真的吗？
Matt?
Your cell, really?
放松点，我有个加密数据包
Relax, I've got
an encryption packet.
你了解我的，我从来都不放松
You know me,
I never relax.
小心你的胆固醇，老家伙
Watch the cholesterol,
old man.
你听起来就像老娘们
You sound like Miriam.
Capel城有什么新动静吗
So, what's new
in Cape Town?
没什么
Nothing, nothing.
我升级了我的目标侦察分析系统，现在搞定了
I updated my Surveillance Target Analysis.
It's complete now.
嗯，那是个安全报告，你离开之前不会到期的
Yeah, that's an exit report.
It's not due until you leave.
确切时间，我要确切时间，什么时候到期？
Exactly. Exactly.
And when is that?
有多长时间了？
How long has it been?
12个月了
Twelve months.
好吧，再过四个月告诉我
Well, talk to me
in another four.
David，我在这儿都快长毛了
David, I'm dying here.
巴黎那边那个职位怎么了，
What's happening
with the post in Paris?
一个空位，有37个申请
One slot,
37 applicants.
他们每一个人都比你有实地经验
Every one of them with more
field experience than you.
要我怎么可能有更多经验呢
How am I supposed to
get more experience?
我整天都看着四面墙
I'm staring at
four walls all day.
我得放弃罗马，然后是柏林
I got passed up on Rome,
then Berlin.
你自己说我的评估非常优秀的
You said yourself, my
evaluation was excellent.
你只要把我的放在Whitford前就行
Just put it in
front of Whitford.
我明白他知道我准备走了
I know he'll see that I'm
ready to go, I'm all in.
Matt,我明白,这一直都很艰难
Matt, I know
this has been hard,
但是系统就是这样运行的
but it's the way
the system works.
但不我什么也不能保证
Look, I'll talk to Whitford about
Paris, but I can't promise anything.
好吧,我得走了
Look, I've got to go.
不要担心，我会罩着你的，好吗？
Don't worry,
I'm looking after you, okay?
嗯，我知道，我知道
Yeah, I know,
I know, I know.
这不是谈判
This is not a negotiation.
是一千万
It's 10 million.
你会拿到文件的，如果钱
You'll get the file,
and if the money
在上午三点前没到帐的话
is not in the account
by 3:00 p.m.
我会找另外一个买家
I'll take it
to another buyer.
那我们怎么知道你会不会之前就卖了
How do we know
that you won't do that anyway?
你不会知道的
You don't.
先生，这边请
Here you are, sir.
Alec，你好啊
Alec, how are you?
Petrus,1972
Petrus, 1972.
你看起来不错啊
You look good.
是吧？
I do, don't I?
M16的事情怎么样了
So, how are things
at MI6?
跟往常一样，还不一样的官僚作风跟吓人的报酬
The usual. Same bureaucratic
bullshit and appalling remuneration.
这就是公务员的生活啊
Life of a government man.
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
所以
So...
Wade：普通的生活
The original file.
日期，交易，名字
Dates,
transactions, names.
高于三倍价格的交易
A bargain
at triple the price.
看看吧
Take a look.
嗯
Hmm.
我等这个已经等了好长时间了
I've been waiting
a long time for this.
wade:tobin....
Tobin...
盒子里面的东西会
What's in that box
is going to make
让你在这个世界上无处可逃的
the world
a smaller place for you,
让我们都无处可逃
for both of us.
我收到你的钱了
I got your account.
交易24小时你会拿到你那部分
You get your cut
24 hours after transaction.
我们的一些老上司看到这些文件公开
Some of our old bosses
aren't going to be happy
会不爽的
these files are out
in the open.
让你很紧张了？
Do I make you nervous?
一直都是这样。很好
Always.
Good.
想要她吗？
You want her?
wade:请听我说
Please, listen to me.
我跟这一点关系也没有
I had nothing to do
with this.
等等
Stop.
走吧
Let's go.
Wade : Tobin 你得相信我
Tobin, you have
to believe me.
对那我一无所知
I knew nothing
about any of that.
你知道有人跟踪你口马
Did you know if
anybody was following you?
不 我当然觉得有人在跟着我
No, I don't think
anybody was following me.
我发誓,tobin,我绝对
I swear on my life,
Tobin, I had absolutely...
慢点
Slow down.
我们要走过去
We're going by foot.
头朝着广场
Head towards the square.
快 快 快
Move! Move! Move!
我们要往西走。
We're heading west.
Holland街，快，快
Holland Street.
Move, move.
先生 不好意思 谢谢
Excuse me, sir.
Thank you.
我叫Tobin Frost
My name is Tobin Frost.
我是Linklater
Link later.
什么时候？
When?
锁定领事馆
Lock down the consulate.
五分钟内在事务厅给我一队人
Get me a team in the Situation
Room in five minutes.
我要我们现有的关于Tobin Frost的所有信息
I want everything we got
on Tobin Frost.
助手：是的 长官
Yes, ma'am.
是他吗？是的
Is it him?
Yep.
whitford知道，
Whitford know?
Linklater:我现正赶过去
I'm on my way there now.
警卫：先生 请把你的手指放在这儿直到我说停下
Sir, place your finger in
there until I tell you to stop.
谢谢
Thank you.
他背着你干了多长时间了，
So how long has he been
playing in your backyard?
我们马上会告诉你答案的
We're working to get you
that answer right now.
就是说你不知道了
Meaning you don't know.
不是 我意思是 我们正在调查
No, meaning,
we're looking into it.
那家伙游手好闲 他花了九年时间
The guy goes rogue,
he spends nine years
出售代理权
selling out the Agency
to all takers.
给俄罗斯 中国 伊朗 凡是你能说得出的他都出售
To Russia, China, Iran,
you name it.
如果没有一个像样的借口的话
The guy is just not
going to prance
那家伙在美国领事馆不会再神气多久了
into an American consulate
without good reason.
Whitford：听着
All right, listen up.
大家都关掉电话
Everybody off the phone.
Tobin Frost刚刚大摇大摆
Tobin Frost has
just waltzed his way
进入南美Cape城的美国领事馆
into a U.S. Consulate
in Cape Town, South Africa.
现在这个人毫无疑问
Now this man,
without question,
是我们抓到的最臭名昭著的商人之一
is one of the most notorious
traders that we've got.
Errinqton，说说他的背景资料
Errington, call up
his background profile.
Errinqton：Tobin Frost在1984年被招入代理处
Tobin Frost was
recruited into the Agency in 1984.
他完成在心理现场工作才能的测定
He tested off the charts in aptitude
for psychological field work.
他第一个任务是在1985年1月,黎巴嫩
His first assignment was in
Lebanon, in January, 1985.
三个月后他抓住了
Three months later,
he captured and flipped
真主党一位高级领导人
a high-ranking
Hezbollah leader.
再接下来几年里
Over the next
several years,
Frost成功招募了一些高价值的人才
Frost successfully questioned and
recruited many high-value individuals.
他因成为一个人类资产专家操纵者而声名远播
He became known as an expert
manipulator of human assets,
然后他还逐字重新编写了政府机构审讯协议
and he literally rewrote Agency
interrogation protocols.
Linklater : Frost为很多活跃的场所服务过
Frost served
in many active theaters,
包括从1995到1998年在利比亚
including Libya
from 1995 to 1998,
1998到2000年在约旦
Jordan, 1998 to 2000.
在他在约旦的任期内
During his tenure
in Jordan,
Frost涉嫌泄露信息给Mossad
Frost was suspected of leaking
information to Mossad,
但是无证可取
but nothing
was confirmed.
十年前，Frost完全脱离组织
Ten years ago, Frost went off
the reservation completely.
目前无人效忠
He currently
has no allegiances
而且被四大洲通绢
and is wanted for espionage
on four continents.
他最后一次出现是在2011年德国汉堡
His last known sighting
is Hamburg, Germany, in 2011.
知道吗 Harlan,我们应该现在立即审问Frost
You know, Harlan, we should
interrogate Frost now.
从他身上榨取点信息出来
Sweat him for
everything he's got.
一旦他回到美国国内，我们的选择会更少
Once he's stateside,
we have fewer options.
在也门我还有个审讯，八小时内能过去
I have an interrogator in Yemen,
can be there in eight hours.
在joburg我已经有个小组了,两小时就能到
I already have a team in Jo'burg
that can be there in two.
我们会把frost带到藏匿之所,在那儿审讯他
We'll take Frost to the safe
house, interrogate him there.
我的人完全有能力处理他
My people are fully
capable of handling this.
他可是Tobin Frost
This is Tobin Frost.
去Joburg
We'll go with Jo'burg.
好吧
Okay.
你得转过去
You must turn around.
救命啊,救命
Help. Help.
意外
Accident.
这里是管家
Housekeeping.
房东：我们有个最后的预订
We have
a last-minute reservation.
用登记的ETA吗
ETA for check-in?
晚上 Freeark保险公司
Sometime tonight.
Freeark Insurance.
收到
Got it.
嗨 嗨
Hello.
Hey.
嘿 你在哪儿？
Hey, where are you?
Weston : Parker刚刚让我完成他的监督文件
Parker just handed me
his oversight papers to finish
你知道吗,他女儿chole患麻疹
and his daughter Chloe's got the
measles, can you believe that?
你要出去多长时间?
How long are you
going to be out for?
我不知道 我不知道
I don't know.
好吧 瞧 我要潜心工作了
Okay. Well, look,
I'm gonna dive into this,
希望一会能见到你 好吗?
and then hopefully I can meet
up with you later, okay?
好的 听起来不错
Yeah, that sounds good.
嘿，嘿。。
Hey, hey...
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
再见 再见
Bye.
Richard:长官 审讯小队已经在飞机上了
Extraction team
is in the air, sir.
他们应该在一小时内着陆
They should be on the
ground within the hour.
我希望那支小队进出城市不超过12个小时
I want that team in and out of
the city in less than 12 hours.
我们甚至都不应该
We're not even
supposed to have
出现在在Cape城 Richards：是的 长官
a presence in Cape Town.
Yes, sir.
Whitford：任何关于和Frost的交流都要严格禁止
Any communications about Frost's
whereabouts are strictly need-to-know.
长官 审讯小队已经在去领事馆的路上了
Sir, the extraction team is en
route to the consulate now.
谁到7-R号了？
Who's reaching out
to 7-R?
Rechards长官
Richards, ma'am.
我要"官家"简单明了
I want
the housekeeper briefed.
高级别首要任务目标己经到了,我需要屋子安静
High-priority target is coming in.
I want the house quiet.
不管什么情况下
Under no circumstances
should there be
直到小队离开都要有通信
any communication
until the team has left.
是的长官
Yes, ma'am.
嗯
Yeah?
有房间吗
Do you have a room?
帐号 Daniel Kiefer
Account?
Daniel Kiefer.
Freeark保险公司的KIEFER
Freeark Insurance.
K- I-E-F-E-R.
Kiefer Freearl保险公司 KIEFER
Kiefer. Freeark Insurance.
K- I-E-F-E-R.
可以进入
You are a go.
你可以进去了
You're good to go.
客房在哪
Hi, I'm Weston.
Guest room?
在那边角落边上 右转两次然后左转一次
It's right around the corner.
Two rights and a left.
原路返回
All the way back.
是Tobin Frost
That's Tobin Frost.
Kiefer：守着他,我们去弄我们的装备
Stay with him. Let's
go download our gear.
pope：是的 长官
Yes, sir.
壁橱在哪？
Linen closet?
走过大厅,直接走到头
Down the hall. Just right
at the end, there.
关掉屋里的监视器
Kill all the surveillance
cameras in this room.
我是Daniel kiefer
My name is Daniel Kiefer.
我们现在在一个屋子里了
We were at
The Farm together.
技术上来说,你比我早一年
Technically,
you were a year ahead.
我来是要让你认识到你的权力
I'm here to make you
aware of your rights.
你现在是在执行国家安全条例
You're being held under
a National Security Directive,
意思就是说,你没有权力,但是你明白是怎么回事
which means you have none,
but you know that.
六百条
Six-hundreds.
你们需要六百条毛巾
The towels,
you need six-hundreds.
那些是350, 375克重
Those are 350,
375-gram weight.
你们会需要六百条的
You're gonna
need six-hundreds.
Kiefer：我想知道你为什么会中Cape城
I want to know the reasons
for you being in Cape Town.
我需要你把来源,联系人,资产都说出来
I want you to name your
resources, contacts, assets,
自从你背判你的国家九年以来
everybody you've
done business with,
你跟哪些人做过交易
traded intel with,
sold secrets to,
出售的机密
in the nine years since you
betrayed your country.
当然,任何你想要的,Daniel
Absolutely.
Anything you want, Daniel.
Kiefer : Khalid Sheikh Mohanmmed持续了20秒
Khalid Sheikh
Mohammed lasted 20 seconds.
他们有六百条
They had six-hundreds.
合法吗
Is this legal?
把他放下来
Bring him down.
抬起来
Bring him up.
刚才多长时间？
How long was that?
好吧，把他放下来
All right,
take him down.
抬起来
Bring him up!
把刀给我
Get me a knife.
Miller?
带Frost进去
Get in there
with Frost.
长官,所有监控器都关掉
Sir, all the security cameras
are down.
重启 我想想看那有什么 -收到
Reboot. I want to see what's out there
Copy that.
Kiefer：伙计们 我们走
Let's go, boys!
快快快
Go! Go! Go!
我们走，快
Let's go, move!
Velez，守住这个角
Velez, take this corner.
Ericksson,去电梯后面
Ericksson,
get the back elevator.
pope,你看到什么了?
Pope, what do you got?
pope：长官我看到大概12个全副装的人在2号围墙
Sir, I see approximately 12
heavily armed men in perimeter two.
Kiefer：好的 伙计们 全面扫描
Okay, gents!
Work fore to aft.
两两一组 2号围墙
Two-by-twos.
Perimeter two.
-Fiefer : Greer ?  -Greel：长官
Greer?
Sir!
-Liefer:Ericksson?  -Ericksson：是的长官
Ericksson?
Yes, sir.
Kiefer:velez?
Velez?
我很好
I'm good!
我们走 伙计们。
Let's go, fellas.
-进来 -手榴弹
Incoming!
Grenade!
Greer？
Greer!
Kiefer：滑行，开始往回走
Step-slide!
Start walking back!
Velez 三轮爆破
Velez!
Three-round bursts!
Velez Gleer在哪？
Velez, where's Greer?
在那儿 长官
He's over there, sir.
孩子 走
Go, son.
这不是测试 这是真的
This ain't a test.
This is the real thing.
你要准备怎么做？
What are you
gonna do?
你别想试我
You don't want
to try me.
-Kiefer：弹夹 -Velez：我们走
Magazine!
Let's go.
Velez 呆在这儿
Velez, stay there!
听我的 呆在这儿
Listen to me
stay there!
妈的
Son of a bitch!
Miller
Miller!
嘿！进这儿来
Hey! Get in here!
嘿 嘿 拿着这个
Hey, hey. Take these.
去看着他
Go watch him.
嘿 他们的目标是我 但是他们想让我活着
Hey, they're here for me,
but they want me alive.
而你 他们会杀了你的
You, they'll kill.
枪膛里有子弹妈？
You got one
in the chamber?
没事的
It's okay.
我记得我第一次派遣去Rio de Janeiro
I remember my first posting.
Rio de Janeiro.
那房间就像现在这样,漂亮的女人
A house like this.
Beautiful women.
并不是一个"客人" 但是我记得规则一
Not one single visitor, but
I remember rule number one.
就是你要对你的"房客"负责
You are responsible
for your houseguest.
而我就是你的"房客"
I'm your houseguest.
时间越来越紧了 他们给了你钥匙
The clock is ticking.
They gave you the keys.
你就要做到你的责任孩子
Do your duty, son.
闭嘴 让我想想
Shut up. Let me think.
你负得起看不住Tobin Frost的责任吗
You want to be the guy
that lost Tobin Frost?
嘀嗒 嘀嗒 嘀嗒
Tick-took,
tick-took, tick-took.
Frost在哪？
Where's Frost?
我们得走了
We're leaving.
他在哪儿
Where is he?
呆在这儿 呆在这儿！等着 别动
Stay here, stay here!
Wait! Don't move!
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey!
Westoll：走
Go!
进后车箱
Get in the trunk.
-你来真的吗？ -是的 进去
Are you serious?
Yeah, get in.
后车箱？进后车箱 马上
The trunk?
Get in the trunk now!
妈的
No!
操作员！基地中心
Ops Center.
三号回话，Victor接九号
Echo Three
Victor Echo Nine.
继续
Go ahead.
我是Weston,7-R号已经被袭,所有人都死了。
This is Weston. 7-R's been hit.
Everyone's dead.
请重复一遍 重复一遍
I need you to repeat that, please.
Say again.
kiefer 他的小队 每个人 都死了
Kiefer, his team, everyone,
they're all dead.
稍等
Stand by.
转接
Transferring.
基地
It's the house.
Linklater我是Weston
Linklater.
This is Weston.
藏匿之所已被毁
The safe house
has been breached.
你的位置？
What's your location?
Westoll：我在Albert路东边
I'm eastbound
on Albert Road.
刚穿过Wood stock
I'm just
passing Woodstock.
我要实时报道
I want eyes on this.
Real-time sat feed.
房客位置在哪
And what's
the location of the guest?
我们逃走了
We escaped.
清楚 你带着"房客"？
Clarify.
Do you have the guest?
是的 我们逃出来了
Yes, we escaped!
听着 我能去到领事馆
Look, I can make it
to the consulate.
但是再没有机会逃开了
There's no chance
for SDR,
我想我后面跟着一大堆人
I think I might have
picked up a tail.
在领事馆门前我们不能发生枪战
We can't have a gun battle
in front of the consulate.
外交灾难
Diplomatic catastrophe.
卫星定位在哪，
Where's that
satellite feed?
被国家侦察卫星拒绝,只能用在战争区域
Denied by National Recon
War theater use only.
快争取点时间
Buy us some time.
不能去领事馆
Do not go
to the consulate.
根据阿尔法O号议案
Follow protocol
Alpha Zero.
保证房客安全 远离道路网
Secure the guest
and stay off the grid.
1800小时重新连接 重复一遍，远离道路网
Reconnect at 1800 hours.
I repeat, stay off the grid.
收到 收到 收到
Copy. copy. copy.
额。。Cape警察已经对房子做出回应
All right, Cape Town police
have responded to the house.
确定  Linldater：保证藏匿之所的安全
Confirmed.
I want the site secured.
我听说有九个人死了
I'm hearing nine dead.
女分析员：开始破损控制
Initiating damage control.
男分析员：正在进行，现在已经控制到NIA了
I'm on it.
Reaching out to NIA now.
当地相关部门要把房子关闭
The locals are going to
have that house locked off.
检查所有交通摄像头，警察报告
Check all the traffic
cameras, police reports...
找出为什么Frost要从进入领事馆
Find out why Frost wanted to go
in that consulate to begin with
以及谁可能会跟着他
and who in the hell else
might be after him.
我们需要把Weston和Frost弄出南非
We need to get Weston and
Frost out of South Africa.
现在我们有任何战术小分队妈？有没有？
Now, do we have any tactical teams?
Anything in play?
额。我在埃及有 但是他们藏得很深
Yeah, I have assets in
Egypt, but they're in deep.
如果我把他们召集起来的话得花个两年时间的
If I pull them out, that would
compromise two years' worth of work.
我能从欧洲争取一只小队到亚洲
I can scramble a team
from Europe or Asia,
不过到少要18个小时
but it's going to
take at least 18 hours.
这样的话，我们只能靠Weston了
At this point,
Weston is all we got.
我要找出来这个Matt Weston是谁,马上
I need to find out who this
Matt Weston is, right now.
女分析员：Matthew Jamesweston
Matthew James Weston.
82年2月24号出生 父母是Terry和Madelineweston
Born 02-24-82 to
Terry and Madeline Weston
出生在纽约,华盛顿港口
in Port Washington,
New York.
他父母跟妹妹死于一场车祸
An assault arrest,
one month after
他父亲血液中酒精含量
both parents and
a younger sister
超过法定两倍
were killed in
a traffic accident
一个月后在一次突击逮捕中
in which his
father's blood-alcohol
他被招幕进来
was twice
the legal limit.
即普经济学学位，从法学院招暮来的
Yale, degree in Economics,
recruited out of Yale law.
在分析力及语言测试中获得相当高分
High marks in analytics
and linguistics at The Farm.
谍报技术能力相当出色
Excellent in
tradecraft skills.
他的女朋友，Ana Moreau是法国人
His girlfriend, Ana Moreau,
is a French national.
在他的报告中描述他们的关系为“紧密且持续的联系”
He reported them as having
"close and continuing contact. "
她是Groote schuur肿瘤学院做了二年住校生
She's a second year resident in the
oncology department at Groote Schuur.
上车
Get in that car.
女分析员：他接受Hotel-Dieu医院里的一个职位
She accepted a
position with Hotel-Dieu Hospital
在巴黎 两周内上班
in Paris,
starts in two weeks.
没有政治背景 很干净
No known political
affiliations. She's clean.
我要你用秘密渠道
I want you to post a car
outside their apartment.
往他们学院寄一辆车
Use back channels.
联系NSA再次核对他们的电话记录和邮件往来
And get NSA to cross-check their telephone
records and their e-mails, please.
是的 长官
Yes, ma'am.
Frost : 额 如果我知道我们要去哪儿的话这事要简单很多
You know, it would be easier
if I knew where we were going.
开车 你只要开车就行 中间那条小路
You just drive, all right?
Just drive, middle lane.
好吧
All right.
嘿 你要干什么 中间那条路
Hey, what are you doing?
Middle lane.
开车就行
Just drive around.
好的 我开着呢
All right.
I'm driving.
很高兴知道你在跟谁说话 你叫什么
Nice to know who you're talking to.
What's your name?
你让我喊破嗓子了
You crushed my windpipe.
啊 你却把我锁在后车箱里了
Well, you locked me
in the trunk.
少来 你又不是海洋委员会的，你是因为你的真名才到这儿的
Come on, you're not NOC. You're
here under your real name.
叫什么
What is it?
weston matt
Weston, Matt.
好吧
All right.
你当房管多长时间了
How long you been
a safe house keeper?
12个月
Twelve months.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
Cape城 这挺好走的
Cape Town,
that's low-level detail.
现在你本应该出城了的
You should have been
out of here by now.
或许是我申请这个任务的
Maybe I requested
the assignment.
或许Lanqley不应该相信你
Or maybe Langley doesn't trust
you with anything else.
你有什么计划，
So, what's your plan?
额，让我猜猜吧，照着议案
Oh, let me guess.
Follow protocol.
方案说如果你的房子被摧毁
Protocol states that
if your house is crashed,
你就得做SDR确保没有跟着你
you do an SDR to make sure
no one's following you.
激活你随行包里的Gps 选择另外一个藏匿之所
Activate your GPS in your Go-Bag,
select another safe house.
你觉得我会让你就这样带我进去？
You think I'm going to
let you just take me in?
我觉得你应该闭嘴
I think you need
to shut up.
我觉得你首先应该考虑一下你的藏匿之所是怎么受到袭击的
I think you need to consider how your
house was attacked in the first place.
你做过了吗 Matt ？
Have you done that, Matt?
他们跟着Kiefer，他们从领事馆就跟着他
They followed Kiefer. They
followed him from the consulate,
所以他们能找到藏身之所
and that's how they
found the safe house.
你不是真的相信我说的吧 是吧？
Come on, you don't really
believe that, do you?
他们怎么能第一个知道我就在领事馆附近？
How did they know I was near the
consulate in the first place?
嗯
Hmm.
但是我喜欢 你知道 你和我 把这事儿搞个明白
But I like this, you know.
You and me, figuring shit out.
就像Hardy Bovs
Like the Hardy Boys.
那个藏匿之所位置很安全
That house was
a secure location.
那些摧毁它的人
Whoever crashed it
不会在加油站旁边停下来然后问最近的藏匿之所在哪儿
didn't stop by a gas station and ask for
directions to the nearest safe house.
人们是被请过来的 有人告诉他们了Matthew
They were invited. Someone
told them, Matthew.
想想 想想你认识的人
Think about it.
Someone you know.
所以你最好问下你自己，你能相信你的房东吗
So you better ask yourself,
can you trust your landlord?
接着说 你骗不了我的
Go ahead, you're not
going to get in my head.
我已经给你洗脑了
I already am
in your head.
他们想要孤立你 Matt
They're going to
isolate you, Matt.
他们开始要真的对你好
They're going to be real
nice to you at first.
他们胳膊抱着你像这样告诉你
They're going to put their arm
around you and tell you things like,
孩子 你的工作很体面 就从这儿结束吧
"You did a decent job, son.
We'll take it from here. "
那时候你就知道你被耍了
That's when you know
you're screwed.
忘了我 他们重点在你
Forget about me. They're
going to focus on you.
他们想试着将你跟我联系起来
They're going to try and make a
connection between you and I.
所以如果这些都是错的
So that if this
all goes wrong,
他们在参议院的听证会上
they'll have something
to fall back on
就有借口可说了
in their little
Senate hearings.
我并不是你今晚唯一的敌人
I'm not your
only enemy tonight.
Whitford：是藏匿之所里的某人
So, it's someone in-house.
这是这件事发生唯一可以解释的
It's the only way this
thing could've happened.
我们己经完全没辙了
We were
completely buttoned up.
我要一份知道这件事的所有人的名单
I want a list of everyone
who knew about this.
背景 关系
Backgrounds, affiliations,
特别是跟Frost的联系
particularly any
connections with Frost.
到这事件发生前每一刻的事倩
Every movement right
up until this operation.
你的审讯小队 他们组织多长时间了，
Your extraction team, how
long had they been together?
我的小队组织起来有六个月了，为什么这么问？
My team had been together
six months. Why?
额 我只是试着把重心放在这
Well, I'm just trying to
get my head around this.
希望有用 谢谢
That will do, thank you.
嗨 嘿
Hello.
Hey.
宝贝 你在哪儿？
Baby, where are you?
我没事 我很好
I'm all right.
I'm okay.
很好
对不起 没有回你电话 我看到未接来电了
I'm sorry I didn't call you
back, I saw your missed calls.
你肯定很担心
You must be worried sick.
没事吧
Is everything okay?
我很好 没事 听着
I'm good.
I'm good. Listen.
听起来有点疯狂
This sounds so crazy.
昨晚诊所受到了点威胁
We had some threats against
the clinic last night,
所以parker和我  我们整夜都在那儿
so Parker and I,
we stayed all night
想试着弄清是怎么一回事儿
trying to get to
the bottom of it.
对不起没回你电话 我应该马上回的
And I'm sorry that I didn't cal! you back.
I should have, right away.
我很担心你
I was so worried.
我知道
I know.
能帮我个忙么，你能走到窗前一会儿吗？
Can you do me a favor? Can you go
over to the window for a second?
为什么？
Why?
你能不能就往窗户外瞅一眼？
Can you just take a quick
look out the window?
我想让你看看是不是有人在外边
I want you to see if
there's anyone out there.
有没有你不认识的车，
Are there any cars
that don't belong?
有没有人在外边晃荡
Anyone hanging
around out front?
有一辆警车
There's a police car.
怎么了
What's going on?
对不起
I'm sorry about this.
我知道这很
I know this is a lot,
但是我们觉得最好
but we felt like
it would be best
不回家，为以防不测
if we didn't go home
as a precaution,
我同意了
and I agree with him.
我知道没什么可担心的 但是我同意了
I know there's nothing to worry
about, but I agree with him.
我觉得你应该去Dena家呆一阵子
I think you should just go to
Dena's for a little while,
就几个小时，我一会会打电话给你的
just for a few hours, and I'll
call you in a little bit.
我们会再一起的 好吗？
And we'll
get together, okay?
好的 我会去的
Okay, I'll go.
好的 我爱你 一会再跟你说 好吗
Okay. I love you. I'll talk
to you soon, all right?
不要担心 没事的 再见
Don't worry. Okay, bye.
她知道你是干什么的？
She know what you do
for a living?
电话那头那个女孩 是个女孩 是吧
The girl on the phone.
It was a girl, wasn't it?
或许是个男的 我不知道
Maybe it was a guy,
I don't know.
我不作评论
I don't judge.
Matthew,干我们这行的别希望跟谁有真正关系
You can't expect to have a real
relationship in our line of work, Matthew.
不要担心 她会离开你的
Don't worry. She's not
going to leave you.
你试着说谎来保护她
See, what happens is, you try
to protect her with lies,
然后就越加一发不可收拾
and then it starts
to add up.
在藏匿之所你说他们会杀了你来得到你
At the safe house you said that
they'd kill me to get to you.
一会儿后,甚至真相
After awhile,
even the truth...
为什么 开始听起来像个谎话了
Why?... starts to
sound like a lie.
是什么
You have something. You got something
that they want. What is it?
她是本地人吗
Is she a local?
不要担心她 是什么，
Don't worry about her.
What is it?
噢 是个女孩
Oh, it is a girl.
你会一直掩饰你的行为 她也会一直相信
You'll keep covering your
tracks, she'll keep believing.
因为她想相信你 因为她需要相信你
Because she wants to,
because she needs to.
那就是我们的工作
That's why we exist, you
and me, that's our job.
为了利用那些
To take advantage of that.
人们宁愿相信
People's desire
to believe.
去信任
To trust.
她不会离开你的 Matthew
She's not going to
leave you, Matthew.
你会离开她的
You're going
to leave her.
我不是你
I'm not you.
男分析员：长官 是对的 我们证实了
Correct, sir.
We verified it.
那是你的人 你来
That is your boy.
You take it.
男分析员：大家待命
Everybody, stand by.
Matty 是我
Matty, it's me.
怎么样了？
How are you holding up?
还行
I'm all right.
召集不了另一队人
Matt, we can't get another
team in for at least 12 hours.
对不起
Sorry.
藏匿之所清空了
We've cleared a new safe house
for you outside the city.
256号寄物柜
There's a Go-Bag located
有个随行包
at locker number 256, Green Point
Stadium Metrorail station.
密码是25122
The combination
is 2-5-1-22.
2-5-1-22.
包里有个GpS
Now, the bag's
got a GPS in it.
会指引你去藏匿之所
It'll direct you
to the safe house.
那地点比较活跃
But you got to be careful,
it's an active location.
所以小心靠近
So, approach
with caution.
Matt
Matt?
知道他们怎么找到Frost的
Do you know how
they found Frost?
你知不知道是谁带着他们过来的？
Do you know who
led them to us?
我们正在找呢
We're working on that.
我们都指望你的Matt
We're counting
on you, Matt.
然后写下你自已的号码
Get Frost to that safe house and
you can write your own ticket.
我会的
I will.
在灯那左转
Left at the light.
去体育馆？
To the stadium?
是的
Yeah.
围巾多少钱？
Hey, scarf.
How much for a scarf?
只要50兰特（100美分
Only fifty rand.
谢谢
Thanks.
把手铐一起
Cuff your hands
together.
一起？是的
Together?
Yeah.
出来
Out.
你确定你不想从这走开
Are you sure you don't
want to just walk away from this?
不能那么干
Can't do that.
是的 你可以 你也应该
Yes, you can.
You should.
走 走 过那条街
Move. Go.
Across the street.
去看比赛 我喜欢比赛
Going to the game.
I like games.
Metrorai  直走
Metrorail,
straight ahead.
直走
Straight ahead.
就在那儿
Right over there.
走
Let's go.
他想绑架我
Help! Help! He's
trying to kidnap me!
哦 哦  哦 哦
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa!
他想绑架我！救命
He's trying to
kidnap me! Help!
他有枪
He's got a gun!
在这儿
He's got a gun! He's
got a gun right there!
我是从事秘密活动的
I'm undercover.
I'm undercover!
大家都冷静
Calm down, sir.
Everybody, calm down!
爬下！爬下
Get down! Get down!
好的！好的
All right! Okay!
把他抓起来！起来
Get him up. Get up.
啊哦 啊哦 啊哦
Ow, ow, ow!
我不知道他为什么抓我
I'm an American citizen. I don't
know what he wanted from me.
冷静
Just calm down.
我是警察 从美国来
Hey, hey, hey. I'm a police officer.
I'm from America.
他叫Tobin Frost
I arrested this man.
His name is Tobin Frost.
你在哪抓住他的？
Where did you take him?
他在医务室
He's in the infirmary.
那儿 那儿 看见了吗？
There, there!
Is that it?
看看 医务室
Top left, second screen from the top!
Look, look, the infirmary.
是的 回放
Right. Go back.
现在 快
Third-tier infirmary,
now! Move!
第三层医务室 现在
Third-tier infirmary.
Go, now!
看见了吧？
Do you see?
别动
Don't move.
Frost!
Frost
frost
Frost!
嘿
Hey!
站住
Stop! Stop!
快离开
Get out the way!
别动
Stop!
不要！站住！
No! Stop!
救护！
Medic!
把枪放下
Drop the gun.
放下枪
Drop it.
我对你负责
I'm responsible for you.
你是对你自己负责
You're responsible
for yourself.
跪下
Get on your knees.
你要杀了我吗？
Are you going
to kill me?
我只杀职业的
I only kill professionals.
广播声：身高约6尺
Height,
approximately six feet.
英国人，穿着体育场安全服
Anglo, wearing
a stadium security jacket.
嫌犯最后被发现时进入了体育场的医疗室
The suspect was last seen entering
Green Point Stadium Metrorail,
体育场中央大厅
stadium concourse.
长官，Frost将会在开普敦做什么是我们的一大威胁
Sir, we have a thread on what Frost
might be doing in Cape Town.
你能放一下。。
Can you bring up...
Alec Wade十五年的奥委会军情六处
Alec Wade.
Fifteen-year NOC at MI6.
破坏，反埋伏，反IED战术
Sabotage, counter-ambush,
counter-IED tactics,
直到四年前在里斯本撕毁任择议定书
until he blew up an op
in Lisbon four years ago
并确凿无疑了
and was put on a desk,
pushing papers.
开普敦警方发现他被人爆头了
Cape Town Police found him
shot through the head,
高功率步枪离领事馆有14个街区
high-powered rifle, 14
blocks from the consulate.
目击者所描述的很符合Frost的形象
Witnesses placed someone
fitting Frost's description
射击时在汽车里
in the car at the time
of the shooting.
所以我们猜测，什么？就是他们是一伙的？
And we think, what? That
they were working together?
他们联合离开在80年代在汉堡的行动
They ran joint operations
in Hamburg in the mid-'80s.
2011年在汉堡最后一次发现Frost的踪迹
Frost's last sighting
was in Hamburg, 2011.
那么Brits有没有说些关于Wade的？
And what are the Brits
saying about Wade?
官方的，他们没说什么
Officially,
they're saying nothing.
非官方的呢？
Unofficially?
他曾被进行过为期5个月的内部惆查
He's been the subject of a
five-month internal investigation.
他们怀疑他出售内部信息
They think he's
been trading intel.
嗯
Hmm.
那么Wade到底泄漏了些什么给Frost
So what the hell
did Wade leak to Frost
这么重要以至于值得杀害我们6个同事
that was so important it was
worth killing six of our men?
我要从军情六处得到更多的信息，所有你能得到的打进电话的账单
I want more details from MI6.
Call in every chit you got.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
Daxid，我要对Daniel和他的小组
David, I want
an internal investigation
进行一次内部调查
into Daniel Kiefer
and his team.
我接到一个Weston打进给David Barlow的电话
I've got Weston calling in
for David Barlow.
Weston：我跟丢了
WESTON ON PHONE
BarloW : Frost ?
Frost?
是的,他跑了
Yeah, he's gone.
在体育场。在我拿到Gps之后他就转移了
After I picked up the GPS,
he created a diversion,
还带走两个警察
took out a couple of cops
at the stadium.
Barlow：知道他要去哪吗？
Any idea
where he's headed?
并不确定，但我可以猜到
Not exactly,
but I will.
我是linklater,你是说他带走了两个警察？
This is Linklater. You
said he took out two cops?
Matt,你继续说
Matt, you're on speaker.
是的,长官,在绿点体育馆
Yes, ma'am.
At the Green Point Stadium.
电视上女播音员：涉及到一个可能的绑架
...involvement
in a possible kidnapping.
疑犯外貌为白种男性,中等身高
The suspect is being described
as a white male of medium build.
体育场的警察报告说你对一个警察开枪了
Stadium police is
reporting you shot a cop.
我是自卫反击
I returned fire
in self-defense.
实际上是Frost放松了戒备
The fact of the matter is,
Frost is on the loose.
我最后14个小时一直在跟着他
I've spent the last
14 hours with him.
他或许说了些和做了些让我能够找到他的蛛丝马迹
He might have said or done something
that could lead me to him.
你现在不要采取行动，现在就去领事馆
You are to stand down,
proceed to the consulate,
向exfil汇报情况，承认所作所为
and present yourself for exfil and debrief.
Acknowledge.
在我汇报情况的时候，Frost就已经跑了
By the time I'm debriefed,
Frost will be gone.
我花了一年的时间调查这
I've spent 12
months researching
镇上的每个角落
every square inch
of this town.
我会找到Frost的，会把他带回来的
I will find Frost
and I'll deliver him.
Weston，我是Harlanwhitford，孩子
Weston, this is
Harlan Whitford, son.
现在，你做的很好，但我们现在要在这里开始
Now, you've done a fine job,
but we'll take it from here.
明白
Understood.
ANA：你好
Hello.
长官，我要求
Sir, I respectfully
request that,
不要把这些记录在案
that exchange not
make it onto his files.
他既没有不称职也没为其他人工作
He's either incompetent or he's
working with somebody else.
不牵扯到Weston
Do not make this
about Weston.
是你的人弄丢了 Frost
It was your guys
that lost Frost.
是你的小组在安全屋里把这弄砸的
It was your team that
folded at the safe house.
我要你俩下载乘航班去开普敦
I want both of you on an
airplane to Cape Town.
FroSt现在正在从这个国家逃出去,去找到他
Frost is trying to get out of the country.
Go find his ass.
找到你了，小东西
There you go, baby.
一张去约翰内斯堡的票
One ticket to Jo'burg.
谢谢
Thank you.
Weston
Police had detained
American NGO worker Matthew Weston
他可能牵扯到枪击事件
as a possible suspect
in the shooting.
今早Weston被捕
Weston had been
detained earlier today,
但是在体育场安全所审问关于枪击案件
but managed to escape while being
questioned by stadium security officials
的时候逃脱了
about his involvement
in the shootings.
嫌犯是一名白种男性，中等身高
The suspect has been described
as a white male of medium build,
外穿一件体育场的安全服
possibly wearing
a stadium security outfit.
亲爱的
Baby
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
我对你撒谎了
I lied to you.
所有的事，非政府组织，Parker
About everything.
The NGO, Parker.
我的工作
My job.
我的家人
My family.
那么你为谁工作
So, who do you work for?
政府
The government.
中央情报局
CIA.
我是说。。
No, I don't...
我不做任何事
I don't do anything.
我在办公室一坐就是一整天，接接电话
I sit around in an apartment
all day I answer the phone.
我需要你离开
I need you to leave.
你需要你为我这样做，行不？
I need you to do that
for me. Okay?
你看
Here.
这有一张去约翰内斯堡的票
This is a ticket
to Jo'burg.
当你到那，你就直接去机场
When you get there, you go
straight to the airport.
那有一班早上去巴黎的航班
There's a 6:00 a.m. flight
to Paris.
拿着这个
Take this.
你拿着，如果有谁要拦着你。。
You take this.
If anyone stops you...
如果有谁要拦着你 如果有谁要拦着你
If anybody stops you...
你认为我是什么人？
Who do you think I am?
别，停下
Stop, Stop
去你的！
Fuck you!
嘿，停下，住手
Hey, stop. Stop it.
我们一周之前就分开了，你之后就没见过我，明白？
We broke up a week ago. You
haven't seen me since, okay?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
离开吧，好不好？
Just leave. Please?
你爱我吗？
Do you love me?
非常爱
Very much.
快快
Go. Go.
快走
Go.
声音：所有的乘客请注意
Attention, all passengers,
20站台，前往LANGA TOWNSHIP的列车
Platform 20
for Langa Township
将在5分钟后出发
departing in five minutes.
Langa Township将在5分钟后发车
Langa Township,
departing in five minutes.
长官，有人用Weston的密码进入我们的系统
Sir. Someone just logged into our
system using Weston's password
访问他的存储的文件
accessing his
stored files.
WHITFORD：是他，他到底要干什么？
It's him. What
the hell is he doing?
我不知道
I'm not sure.
我要看看他在查看什么
I want to see
what he's looking at.
RUCHAROs：他在查看一份很久之前的报告
He's pulled an old report
关于生活在兰加乡区的监测目标。
on surveillance targets living
in the Langa Township area.
那是一个CARLOS VILLAR的一个轮廓，尼加拉瓜国家
It's a profile of Carlos
Villar, a Nicaraguan national.
他是一个出名的文件伪造者
He's a known
document forger.
WHITFORD：给我拷贝一份Weston的那份报告
Get me a copy
of Weston's report.
RICHARDS：是的，长官
Yes, sir.
女分析：退出了，长官，他离开了
Logged off, sir.
He's gone.
在长街的一个网吧
An Internet cafe
on Long Street.
像一个黑色的Dorian Gray
Like a black
Dorian Gray.
那是，最近怎么样，兄弟？
That's right.
How you doing, brother?
进来，好的
Come in.
Yes, sir.
ILLANA ？
Illana?
ILLNA：好啊
Hi.
CARLOS：我们有客到
We have a guest.
ILLANA，见到你很高兴．
illana.
Good to meet you.
Joseph，我女儿
Joseph, my daughter.
你好  你好
How are you?
Hello.
CARLOS：我女婿
My son-in-law.
ILLANA：喝茶吗？
May I offer you some tea?
不用，我们去楼上
No, we're going
upstairs.
我记得
I remembered.
你甚至可以让它呼吸．
You even let it breathe.
太长时间的牺牲会使一个人变得铁石心肠
"Too long a sacrifice Can
make a stone of the heart
哦，什么时候它会满足？
"O when may it suffice?
那是天堂的一块
"That is Heaven's part"
以前的时候，一瓶便宜的
In the old days,
a cheap bottle
果不其然塔卡纳能让我们开心一整晚
of Flor de Cana kept us
happy all night.
嗯嗯，味道变了
Mmm. Tastes change.
人变了
People change.
人是不会变的
People don't change.
我们老了
We grow old.
我们中的一些开始慢慢适应
And some of us adapt.
和学会怎么享受这平淡生活的快乐
And learn how to enjoy
simple pleasures of life,
就如一个家庭，一个家
like a family, a home.
至于你...
And for you...
你的那杯你现在装着些什么
What's in that glass
right now, for you,
因为它永远是一样好
is as good as it's
ever going to be.
总有一天你会明白的
One day you'll understand.
你对过去挂念太多啊
You got more past
than future, you learn.
这是什么？一种接入器？
What is this?
An intervention?
我以为你已经死了
I thought you were dead.
那么，在这么多年后
So, what brings you to my home
in the middle of the night
是什么把你大半夜的带到我家的？
after all these years?
哦哦
Ooh.
爸爸？
Papa?
嗯呢
Uh-huh.
我们要走了
We're going.
好的，路上注意
Okay, be careful.
知道了爸爸
Okay, Papa
你要怎么处理这些？
What are you
going to do with this?
赚些钱
Make some money.
让我用下你的眼镜
Let me borrow
your glasses.
这就是了，听着
That's it. Listen.
我需要一个新的护照，身份证还有驾照
I'm going to need a new passport,
photo ID, driver's license,
全部的这些家当，你能帮我办到吗？
the whole shebang.
Can you do that for me?
当然
Yeah.
你确定？
You sure?
嗯
Yes.
Weston从未在领事馆露过面
Weston never
showed at the consulate.
他刚刚访问我们的安全服务器
And he was just
accessing our secure server,
寻找一个人，以创建一个别名包。
searching for someone
to create an alias package.
你试图离开这个国家
He's trying to
leave the country.
或许他在跟着Frost
Or he's going
after Frost.
瞧瞧在足球体育场发生了些什么
Look at what
happened at the soccer stadium.
这家伙让Frost逃跑了
This guy
let Frost escape.
我想Weston叛敌了
I think Weston's turned.
我知道这个人
I know this boy.
一直在寻找一个机会证明自己
He's been looking for a
chance to prove himself.
他想试着把Frost带过来
He's trying to
bring in Frost.
Llnklater：快点儿，David
Come on, David.
你并没有看见证据
You're not
seeing the evidence.
这不是我最好的成绩
Not my best work.
但是出于时间的压力，还行吧
But given the pressure
of time, it's passable.
一旦我出城了
It's good.
I'll wire you the money
还行，钱我会电汇给你的
as soon as
I get out of town.
Tobin,不这这么干，这不一样
Tobin, don't do this.
It's different.
你不需要金钱
You don't need the trouble,
you don't need the money.
你能给的是。。。
You can give it...
Illana : CarlOS
Carlos!
Illana
Illana!
Illana : CarlOS
Carlos!
CarlOS : Illana
illana!
CarlOS
Carlos.
Carols
Carlos!
走
Go.
他在房顶上
He's on the roof!
快！快
Go! Go!
进去！
Get in the car!
他们以为他们能跟我似的呢
They think they can
come at me like this.
得做得更好才行
Have to do it a whole
lot better than that.
妈的
Shit!
Matt你是怎么找到我的？
Matt, how'd you find me?
并不难
It wasn't that hard.
我们走
Let's go.
等等，等等
Wait, wait, wait.
你替谁卖命？
Who do you work for?
Weston：谁派你过来的？
Who sent you?
谁派的？
谁？
Who?
Vargas
Vargas.
谁是Vargas ?
Who's Vargas?
你不想活了吗？
You want to die?
谁是Vargas ?
Who's Vargas?
Matt
Matt.
CIA
CIA.
CIA ! CIA
CIA! CIA!
报告？
Report?
在Langa乡有枪战
There was a shootout
in the Langa Township.
两个犯罪现场,一个在Carlos Villar住处
Two crime scenes. One at the
residence of Carlos Villar.
他是个文件伪造者
He's a document forger.
另外一个在附近一个公寓
The other in
a nearby tenement.
最后一次是在哪儿看到Frost的？
And where was
Frost last seen?
公寓
Tenement.
在Villar家玩得愉快
Have fun at Villar's.
一会见
We'll meet up later.
关于Ana你是对的
You were right
about Ana.
那是她的名字
That's her name.
Frost：不好意思
Sorry to hear that.
大多数案件主管都结过三，四次婚
Most case officers get
married three, four times.
你呢？
You?
一次
Once.
Weston：在那儿你会崩溃的
You're falling apart
over here.
Matthew，不要杀害无辜的人
Don't kill innocent people,
Matthew.
什么？
What?
Bermuda一个很小的临时跑道
Air traffic controller,
a tiny airstrip in Bermuda.
George Edwart Cox 我记得他的名字
George Edwart Cox,
I remember that name.
Edwart有个T
Edwart, with a
我的一个内部人员说他正在组织运送武器
My inside officer said he was
organizing arms shipments,
他只是个伙计
but he was just an air traffic controller.
He was just a guy.
我对他的脑袋开了一枪
I put a bullet
in his skull.
基地的人进来,把他换成他们其中的一个人
Black Ops came in, they replaced
him with one of their own,
那晚随着湾流冲向了大海
and crashed a Gulf stream
in the ocean that night.
他们全家都在飞机上
The thing was, the family
that was on the plane...
丈夫是一个告密者
The husband,
he was a whistleblower.
整个过程就是要
The whole thing was about
阴止他在国会的听证会上揭发整个网络
stopping him from
testifying about wet works
揭发整个工作网络
to a congressional hearing.
这就是为什么你要离开？
Is that why you left?
不
No.
第二天我像什么都没发生一样回来工作
I went back to work the next day
like nothing ever happened.
这方面你就是高手
You practice anything a long
time, you get good at it.
于是它听起来就像真的一样
You tell a hundred lies a day,
it sounds like the truth.
每人个都在背叛别人
Everyone betrays everyone.
这真是个狗屁借口
That's a shitty excuse.
嗯，我曾经跟你一样啥也不懂
Yeah, I used to be
innocent like you.
将自已层层包裹
Wrap myself up
in the flag...
我会带着你的
I'm going to take you in.
谢谢
Good for you.
Barlow
Barlow.
目击都确认两个人
LINKLATER ON PHONE Witnesses
identified a pair of men
根据描述是Weston和Frost
fitting Weston and
Frost's description
一起离开这儿了
leaving this
location together.
所以他离开了
So, he pulled it off.
Weston正在帮助还有唆使一个逃亡者
Weston is aiding and
abetting a fugitive.
你错了
You're wrong.
他会把它带到藏匿之所
If he's with Frost, he's
taking him to the safe house.
那就是我们该去的地儿
That's where we got to be.
好吧，好的
Fine. Fine.
在Old Malmesbury路的十字路口见
Meet me at the crossroads
at Old Malmesbury Road.
Keller：你是谁？
Who are you?
Weston ?
You Weston?
把枪给我
Give me the shotgun.
这是怎么回事？
What the hell is this?
你是谁？
Who are you?
藏匿之所的管家
I'm Keller.
Safe house keeper.
Oscar whiskey6
Authorization Index, Bravo
Four Seven Oscar Whiskey Six.
进去，走
Inside. Let's go.
左边
To the left.
慢点
Slowly.
但这肯定不是协议上写的
I don't know who trained you,
man, but this sure as hell
客房在哪
ain't protocol.
Where's the guest room?
问题是，我们真的没有
That's the thing, we
don't really have one.
那儿，在那儿
In there. In there.
铐着他，铐在管子上
Cuff him.
To the pipe.
出去，那边
Out. Over there.
好吧
All right.
控制室
Control room.
怎么说都行，哥们儿，都你说了算
Whatever you say, man
It's your rodeo.
呼叫 让我听见
Call it in.
Let me hear it.
“房东”
Landlord.
我的房客在这儿
My guest is here.
账号？
Account?
受限Abaresque
Abaresque Limited.
和房客？
With a guest?
是的，数据包发送
Yeah, package delivered.
临时安排
Confirmed.
Pickup scheduled.
他们过来了
They're on the way.
现在能把枪放下了吧？
Can we at least
put the gun down now?
谢谢，Clayton,再见
Thanks, Clayton. Bye.
是一个芯片
It's a microchip.
什么？
What?
来自M16
That was
my guy from MI6.
Wade把他的手指放在芯片上了
Wade got his hands
on a microchip.
上面是什么？
And what was on it?
只有Wade知道
Only Wade knew,
但是我觉得这样假设为什么
but I think
it's safe to assume
他跟Frost一起很靠谱
that's why he
hooked up with Frost.
卖掉它
To sell it.
我们出发吧
Let's get moving.
很长的一天，是吧？
Long day, huh?
Tobin Frost
I can only imagine.
Tobin Frost.
那个人是个传说
That man's a legend.
我希望你能学到点什么
I hope you
picked up something.
你不会接受更好的教育
You ain't going to
find a better education.
这是我看到了最兴奋的事
This is the most
excitement I've seen.
你是我十个月以来第一个房客
You're the first guest
I've had in 10 months.
但是你什么也不知道是吧？
But you wouldn't know
anything about that, right?
你只是有个城市的职位派遣
You got a city posting.
是吧,夜生活，海滩
Yeah, nightlife, beaches.
到处逛的小妞儿
Little ladies
running around everywhere.
是的
Yeah.
我挺嫉妒的
I'm jealous.
来杯咖啡？
You got coffee?
好的，在柜子里
Yeah, it's in the cupboard.
哪儿？
Where?
拿到了
Want me to get it?
I got it.
你为什么会在Cape城
Why are you
in Cape Town?
告诉我，为什么？
Tell me now. Why?
那是什么？
What is it?
一份清单
A dirt list,
laundry list.
五年前以色列情况局，编译的勒索名单
Israeli Intelligence, five years
ago, compiled blackmail intel.
德国情报局，MI6
Corrupt agents,
German Intelligence, MI6...
CIA ?
CIA?
是的
Yes.
我们得离开了
We got to get away.
人们得离开这里
We got to get out of here.
妈的
Ah, shit.
别别
Don't, don't, don't.
不，别把我留在这里
No, don't leave me here,
please.
不要
Don't do it.
Matt ?
Matt?
嘿
Hey.
怎么样了？
How you doing?
我以你为荣
I'm proud of you.
你所做的
And what you pulled off.
你会成为一个案件主管的
You're going to make
a hell of a case officer.
Frost在哪儿？
Where's Frost?
他走了
He's gone.
到处都是血
Place is a wreck.
Blood everywhere.
他受伤了还是
Was he injured or...
我猜他杀了Keller
I guess you know
he killed Keller.
不
No.
是我杀的
I killed Keller.
Frost杀了Keller
Frost killed Keller.
他也杀了Linklater
He killed Linklater, too.
他在找什么？
Did he talk about anything?
Anything he was after?
他身上有什么东西吗？
Anything he might
have had?
文件
The file.
文件？
The file?
你们要找的文件
The file that you're on.
关系到其它很多人
Along with a lot
of other people.
很重要的人
Important people.
Barlow:听我说
Listen to me.
如果有人监视你的一举一动
What would you do
你会怎么办？
if someone is
watching your every move?
你也许并不以有些人为荣
Some maybe
you're not proud of.
但是相信我，一定会有一些你并以之为傲的人
And you will have some you're
not proud of, believe me.
然后以之来对付你？
And then tries to
use it against you?
有些事你会不得不做的
You would do
what you have to do.
有些事你会不得不做的
You would do
what you have to do.
文件在哪？
Where's the file?
Matt, the file.
Where is the file?
你去死吧
You're a dead man.
是的，还早呢
Yeah, a long time now.
Frost在这儿
Frost is here.
我们走
Let's go.
我们抓到他了
We got him.
妈的什么工作
A hell of a job.
你闻到了吗？
You smell that?
很好的酒
Pinotage. It's a good grape.
Great wine.
Pinogage酒很.....
Local grape.
Pinotage is great...
我不想你把这个弄丢了
I don't want you
losing this one.
它很值钱
It's worth a lot
of money.
你是个好孩子,Matty
You're a good boy,
Matty.
你知道你是什么样的人
You know what you are.
嘿
Hey.
我知道你不是那样的人
I know what you're not.
你比我好多了
You're better than me.
只要比我好就行
No, it's okay,
just be better than me.
答应我
You promise me.
好的
Yeah.
额，我们...
Well, let's...
走
Let's go.
我必须起来，我必须起来
I just got to get up.
I need to get up.
坐着
Stay.
嘿
Hey...
这就是所发生的详细的一切
That's exactly
as it happened.
很明显，这种情况需要
Obviously,
this situation needs
特殊手段才能处理
to be handled with a
certain amount of finesse.
还有其它人看过这份报告吗？
Has anybody else
seen this report?
没有，长官，还没有
No, sir. Not yet.
Matt，我肯定这事不出意料
Matt, I'm sure this
comes as no surprise,
这份报告里一些东西要被修饰一下
but parts of this report are going to
have to be altered for national security.
哪些，长官？
Which parts, sir?
额..
Well...
David Barlow不能对所发生的
David Barlow can't
be held responsible
担负责任，比如藏匿之所
for what happened
to the safe house.
我们不需要丑闻
We just don't
need the scandal.
那不是事实
But, sir, you and I both know
that, that is just not the truth.
人们不再需要事实了Matt
People don't want
the truth anymore, Matt.
这太糟糕了，让他们永埋地下吧
It's too messy.
Keeps them up nights.
但是我告诉你我想做的
I'll tell you what I am
willing to do, though.
我觉得局里太低估你了
I think the Agency has
grossly underestimated you,
我会推荐你一个高级案件主管的职位的
and I'm recommending you for a
senior case officer position.
提供你仍然想要的
Provided you still want it.
那真是一个慷慨的建议，长官
That's a generous
offer, sir.
只有一件事你需要清楚
There's just one thing you
need to clarify for me.
当然
Of course.
Frost可能给一些很重要的情报
Frost may have been
carrying some vital intel.
一份文件
A file.
但我在这报告里任何地方都没有看到
I'm not seeing that
anywhere in this report.
文件里是什么，长官？
What was
on the file, sir?
坦率的说是一些很有毁灭性的东西
Something that, quite frankly,
could be very damaging
对这个部门，对我们的盟友来说
to the Agency
and to our allies.
我不明白为什么Frost甚至对我提都没提这事
I don't see why Frost would even
mention something like that to me.
不，我认为他不会，是吧？
No, I suppose he wouldn't,
would he?
但是你知道如果文件内容泄露的话
You realize, though,
that if that file did leak,
会怎样吧？
what would happen
to the person responsible?
它会被逮捕，长官
That person would
be arrested, sir.
他在冒很大的危险
He'd be risking
everything.
他会在全世界的情报部门全面树敌
He'd have enemies in every
intelligence agency in the world.
在CIA眼里,他就像是Tobin Frost
In the eyes of the CIA he'd
be just like Tobin Frost.
关于文件Frost什么也没说,长官
Frost didn't say anything
about a file, sir.
好吧，孩子
All right, son.
休息几天
Take a few days off.
下周开始工作
We'll get you
started next week.
谢谢
Thank you.
想想我们的谈话，好吧？
And think about our
conversation, would you?
我会的
Will do.
从现在开始我就会的，长官
I'll take it
from here, sir.
其他媒体..
...and other media outlets
从一个未知来源接收到一个谈话文件
received a controversial file
from an anonymous source.
国际情报团体仍然
The international intelligence
community is still reeling
高度机密文件
from the release of so many
highly classified documents
以及广布的腐败和犯罪活动信息
and the revelations of widespread
corruption and criminal activity
的泄露头晕目胜
at the CIA,
the BND, and MI6.
报道1：由于英国情报机构
...is in
an uproar over the lack
的疏忽引起轩然大波
of oversight given to
British Intelligence,
要求交出负有此责任的探员
demanding accountability
of the rogue agents.
MI6的官员正在全面合作
Officials at MI6
are fully cooperating.
报道2 : Merkel总理承认
Chancellor
Merkel insists that the BND
已经确认了腐败探员
has already identified
the corrupt agents
包括情报特工
and contained
the intelligence breach.
她已经保证国际同仁
She has ensured her
international counterparts...
报道3：起诉将在本周进行
Indictments are
now expected within the week,
国会要求副主任Harlan Whltford
and Congress has demanded that
Deputy Director Harlan Whitford
证明参议院附属委员会
testify before
a Senate subcommittee
决定多少CIA人员
in an effort to
determine how many people
涉及此案
at the CIA are
involved in this
以及腐败上至几级
and just how far up
the corruption reaches.
更多精彩请关注HDChina.org